gnomonschool.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy | Gnomon | Gnomon

## What information do we collect?

We collect information any time you use our site, including when you register, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To process transactions   
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
  * To send periodic emails   
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.   
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Remarketing

We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise Gnomon across the internet. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the Gnomon website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. This cookie does not identify you or give Google or us access to your computer. The cookie essentially states, "This person visited this webpage, so show this person ads related to that webpage." Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and to only display ads that are relevant to you. Learn more about Google’s use of cookies by visiting <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>.

## Analytics Services

This site uses the Lucky Orange analytics system to help improve usability and the customer experience. Lucky Orange may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, and scrolling activity. No information sent to Lucky Orange is personally identifiable.

To view and manage any data that Lucky Orange may have collected about you or to opt out of any future tracking, please visit the [Lucky Orange Privacy Policy](https://www.luckyorange.com/privacy.php).

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'My Account' page.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the contact page.

This policy is powered by Trust Guard.
